Gifty Arthur

University of Ghana, Computer Science giftarthur@gmail.com +233 248 373 3574

Profile

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a solid foundation in machine learning, deep learning, and natural language processing, I excel in developing AI solutions that optimize operations, enhance user experiences, and solve complex challenges. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Hardworking, good communication skills, and a team player, with core values of honesty, transparency, and integrity.

Personal Information

Nationality: Ghanaian

Residence: Ghana

Date of Birth: 4th September 2001

Gender: Female

Marital Status: Single

Religion: Christian

Education

2019- 2023

University of Ghana - Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

2016 - 2019

Swedru Senior High School, Central Region, Ghana - Basic Education, General Science

Work Experience

October 2023-Present

Odd Haus Company Limited - Designer / Developer

- Develop websites for new projects.
- Handle Social Media designs.

September 2022- November 2022

University of Ghana, Computer Science Department - Teaching Assistant Intern

- Developed Mobile applications and websites.
- Assisted in building the Financial Dashboard for the University of Ghana

August 2019 – July 2020

Swedru Omega Preparatory School - Academic Tutor

- Taught Mathematics for primary grade 4, 5, and 6
- Taught Religious and Moral Education for primary grade 4, 5 and 6

Volunteering

March 2022

SISCODE VOLUNTEER

- Educating young girls about technology.
- Empowering young girls to venture into STEM education.

August 2019

Camfed Ghana

- Educating Adolescents on Personal Hygiene.
- Donations of Books, pens, and Sanitary pads to the student of Gomoa Manso

Skills

Programming Languages and Frameworks: JavaScript, Reacts, HTML5, Tailwind CSS

Microsoft Office: Office Suite

Language Proficiency

English

Certifications

• Completion of Soft Skills by jobber man Ghana.

REFERENCES

DR. EBENERZER OWUSU

Head Of Department of Computer Science

+233244362054

Email: eowusu2012@gmail.com

DR. SOLOMON MENSAH

Senior Lecturer of Computer Science

+233241197511

Email: smensah03@ug.edu.gh